Seino, here we are!
Now, everyone, let's relax and have a free talk while eating snacks!
It's past noon and I'm hungry!
I'm hungry!
We have a little place to eat
Join us.
1:30?
1:30.
Still another 1:30.
Not yet.
It's 1:30.
Yes, sir.
Um...
I've got to tell you something.
It's not just candy.
It's got a lot of stuff in it.
Russian Greats?
It's like, you know, it's like, one of them or something.
I don't even know what's in it. I don't know what's in it.
I don't know what's in it.
We don't know, but we're professionals.
I don't know, but we're professionals.
I don't think we should make them sorry.
Yes, I agree.
Delicious and fun
The way it is
Russian rule
Now that I've been an animal
I can prove it.
So today with Ipponchan
We're going to have a great time at GREEK TALK
With this pastry
I'm looking forward to spending time with you.
Here we go!
Are you into that?
Thanks, but I just shared with you that I'm really into hot milk.
Oh, that's nice. It's a real mystery.
Without anything in it? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm into ordering it without anything in it. Thank you.
I'm pretty sure that's not in there. Definitely not. This one is.
This is definitely not in there. There's no way to put it in there.
It's the wrong way to put it. What's in it? What's in it? It's the way they put it in, with the factory showing.
There's a chance... that it's the one with the factory on it.
Bon appétit.
Ow, ow, ow.
Oh, it's pink.
I'm sure it's delicious.
Mentaiko.
Oh, no!
Delicious!
Ayahaeng is here.
Ayahaeng even if you go to Shanghai Kung
Cream puffs are the scariest!
I've eaten nothing like this.
It's got a spacer on it.
So you want some cream puffs? Everyone!
Just eat it like it's normal.
Wait a minute.
But usually, when you put it in, you pass it to me.
No, no, no, guys, you have to go natural.
It's good.
Delicious.
TalkTalk
Yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy!
I'm getting hungry
I'm getting sleepy.
I think you're giving out too much extract.
Yummy, yummy, yummy!
I'm starving.
I did a puzzle recently.
I made you check it out.
What's that? I don't know.
I don't know, I've never done a puzzle before.
You smell pretty.
You always do.
I still think it's a cute puzzle.
I've never done puzzles before.
No, I'm just saying, you're so enthusiastic.
I'm sure you are.
I'm elated.
But I think I started around New Year's.
Yes, I did.
But, you know, I finished it right away.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I thought I liked it.
Oh, really?
Wow.
What did you like about it? What did you like about it? Puzzles.
Puzzles. The feeling you get when you're stuck.
It takes me three or four minutes to put this one together.
It takes me three or four minutes to put it together.
It takes me four minutes, that's for sure.
That's for sure.
That's right.
The first one, it's like a little bit of a whammy to get one on.
It just goes on and on and on and on and on.
That's the kind of game you like to play.
I like the mission-completion kind of thing.
I like the feeling of taking my time and not being rushed.
That's a bit much.That's a bit much, don't you think?
I don't get it.
Can I have an éclair?
Hmm?
Oh, yeah?
Why are you doing that?
We're eating each other again.
Well, do you want half?
No, I don't.
Itzki like a dessert in our house!
Ryo, ma'am.
See you later!
My favorite character, my favorite arpeggiator.
If it's a puzzle, I'd like to do it.
I want to do the Ghibli ones.
He wants to decorate the Panacea.
I want to decorate my house.
I don't know...
Heh...
This is a little...
It's normal.
Can I eat it?
But I'll eat one of each.
Yeah, no way.
I didn't know they were all lined up like this.
That's why I drank it.
That was fast.
Yes, sir.
I feel like I'm losing my hand.
I'm scared.
I want to drink my tea first.
Did you drink it?
Like voluntarily?
Yeah.
When I'm working here...
You eat a lot, don't you?
Yeah, a lot.
But I really appreciate it.
I can eat in no time.
And it's easy for everyone to follow.
It's easy to get to.
There's a lot of people lined up.
Everyone's on their cell phones.
What's that smirk on your face?
You there?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
That was delicious!
Thank you so much for the food!
How was it?
I don't know, I don't know... the first time...
If I had to guess, I'd say the yuzuki is by far the best.
It hurts here.
What was in it?
There was so much wasabi in it!
I mean, it's so green when it's pointed like this...
It's overflowing, it's overflowing, it's overflowing!
It's so overflowing that when I put it in my mouth, the first thing on my tongue was the wasabi.
I don't know what kind of smell I put in it.
I didn't let him smell it at all.
I was smelling it the most.
It's just that cream and horseradish are usually mixed together too much.
They don't go well together.
Yeah, it's just... it's all mixed together and it smells really bad.
One time?
I think there was condensed milk the second time.
There's something sweet in there, too.
I think it was really sweet.
I don't know. Yuzuki.
They have condensed milk.
Oh, I wonder if that's it.
Oh, there's condensed milk in it.
I knew it was in there.
Wasabi and condensed milk.
Well, maybe he got two.
How many?
How many did you get?
Raise your hand if you got a packer.
Yes, sir.
I thought I might have.
Probably with the same wasabi.
The same wasabi at the same time as the first cream puff.
But the first cream puff was wasabi.
I didn't understand.
I saw it before you did.
That's amazing.
It's amazing.
I can eat wasabi.
I can eat it, but there's not enough to go around.
It was so bad, but I thought I could eat it.
I've been here the whole time
Hagizuki stands out so much!
I knew I'd never been there before
Oh, wait, there's eclairs in there!
They don't have eclairs, do they?
I don't know... ours had a lot of chocolate shavings.
There were a lot of shavings.
The last one.
I think it's in there.I think it's in there.
There was nothing in it.
It was just cream puffs, but they were in there.
They were just delicious.
The last one I had had a lot of condensed milk.
Oh, really?
That's what it looked like.
Did it have anything condensed milk in it?
Condensed milk and wasabi.
Condensed milk and wasabi went well together.
Maybe the condensed milk was a little too much.
It's too sweet. It's shocking.
Oh, condensed milk and wasabi.
Oh, it wasn't right.
You look disappointed.
I'm not sorry.
I'm kind of disappointed.
I'm not disappointed.
You want to try some?
It's not right.
Once again, you all did a great job.
Please give me a "Good" button for a job well done.
That's right.
Please watch it again, and rewind it.
It says, "Good luck.
Okay, well, good luck.
That's a start.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel.